SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Full stack software engineer with 9 years of experience in fashion production, working collaboratively in a fast-paced team environment. My experience of living in Korea, Chile, Argentina, Italy, and the United States gives me unique skills in intercultural communications. My proficiency in various languages has uniquely suited for training quickly in computer languages, developing full stack applications with JavaScript, React, Ruby, and Rails using SQL databases and RESTful API architecture.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Skills: JavaScript, React, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, SQL, REST APIs, HTML, CSS, GitHub
- Languages: Korean (Native), English (Native), Spanish (Fluent), and Italian (Intermediate)

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

SCCO – GitHub | Demo

Check out cosmetics' ingredients at a glance

- Implemented Chart. is library to conveniently illustrate ingredients used in each product
- Utilized React, Rails, CSS, Chart.js, Figma and Render to create and launch the web application in the cloud
- Established authentication and access control systems utilizing sessions and cookies storage for secure user access

MindGarden - GitHub | Demo

Express and keep track of your mental feelings journal

- Developed with Sinatra API backend making use of Active Record to access and store data in database
- Used Tailwind CSS open source framework for efficient responsive design

Gallerology - GitHub

An artwork logbook application that allows users to track and catalog artists and their notable works encountered while visiting museums and galleries.

- Utilized Ruby on Rails and implemented full CRUD actions writing RESTful API functionalities
- Designed the database schema and coded the DB logic with Active Record and PostgreSQL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Q4 Designs LLC, *Production Coordinator* | New York, NY

Nov 2016 – July 2022

- Executed the entire production cycle of \$16 million worth Reebok Outerwear division utilizing Samsung OMS and Blue Cherry software systems, and collaborating across multiple teams.
- Performed thorough research and analyzed data for the season's merchandising styles, budget planning, and inventory allocation to ensure the business goals are met.

Amerex Group, Assistant Merchandiser | New York, NY

Aug 2013 – Nov 2016

• Communicated with various divisions within and outside of the company to organize and manage multiple projects, such as production orders, WIP reports, cost sheets, and testing- simultaneously. Meticulously followed up with seasonal production delivery deadlines and customer compliances to prevent chargebacks and maximize margin.

LVMH Inc, *Emilio Pucci Buying Intern* | New York, NY

Jan 2013 – May 2013

 Created and presented reports analyzing sales data, monitoring purchase orders and grouping products by price point to inform retail store inventory management decisions.

EDUCATION

Flatiron School | New York, NY

Certificate, Full-Stack Software Engineering

Aug 2022- Nov 2022

Fashion Institute of Technology – SUNY | New York, NY

Bachelor of Science in International Fashion Merchandising Management

May 2013

3.8/4.0, Summa cum laude, Dean's List (all semesters)

Minor: Italian

Polimoda International Institute of Fashion Design and Marketing | Florence, Italy

Study Abroad Program in International Fashion Merchandising Management